https://www.harmanaudio.com/terms.html

FREE SHIPPING. Learn More | FREE EXTENDED RETURN SHIPPING. Learn More
Last Updated:  June 29, 2020
These Terms of Sale are applicable only to orders by and for residents of the 48 contiguous United States. These Terms of Sale are further subject to Harman’s Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.
Placing an Order
By placing an order with us, you are offering to purchase a product or service.  You represent to us that you are at least 18 years old, that all information provided to us with your order is true and accurate, and that you are an authorized user of the payment method provided.  Harman reserves the right to limit, reject, modify, or cancel orders that, in our sole judgment, appear to be from unauthorized parties, including resellers.
Product pricing and product availability are shown on this website, however the website may contain errors. Pricing or availability may be subject to change at any time without notice.  Harman is not bound by its offers or any prices on the website.  Harman reserves the right to modify or cancel your purchase for any type of error on the website.
To place an order, simply add the desired items to your Shopping Cart. You can add, delete, update, or change the quantities of products in your cart while you shop the site. Once you are ready to buy, proceed to check out to enter your shipping and payment information to complete your order. You can complete your order as a guest or by opening a harmanaudio.com user account. By opening a harmanaudio.com user account, you can quickly access product support, updates and promotions. When you send an order, Harman may verify certain items before the order is fulfilled, including without limitation your personal information, your payment information, and your creditworthiness.
Without incurring any liability, Harman reserves the right to refuse any order, correct any inaccuracies or omissions on its website, change or update information for products or services offered, and to modify or cancel your order at any time without notice, whether or not the order is confirmed. If we modify your order, we will attempt to give you prior notice in case you decide to cancel the order.  If Harman cancels your order, we will attempt to notify you via the contact information you provided with your order.
Once your order is submitted, you will receive a printable order confirmation screen detailing your order. You will also receive an order confirmation e-mail which will include your order details. Please be sure to save this order confirmation and print out a copy. This is your receipt for proof of purchase; your merchandise will not include an additional receipt. You will need this receipt if you ever require warranty service from any of our authorized repair centers throughout the U.S.
It typically takes one to two business days to process and ship your order. Once your order has shipped, we will email a shipping confirmation, including tracking number(s). The shipping carrier requires one business day from that time to validate the tracking information.
Payment
harmanaudio.com accepts payment via PayPal, Visa, MasterCard, and American Express.
You will be charged once your order has shipped with the exception of PayPal orders.  PayPal orders are charged in full upon placing the order.
In case of PayPal payments, you will be charged immediately, but in the event you choose PayPal Credit after checking out with PayPal, you may leverage the credit terms provided for future payments or monthly installment as provided by PayPal at the time of order.
Please note that certain orders are subject to a 24-hour verification period to protect all parties from unauthorized credit card use. To assist in minimizing unauthorized card usage, please ensure that your credit card company has all of your current information on file including any alternate or authorized shipping addresses.
If your payment method is charged for an order that is later modified or cancelled, Harman will issue you a refund.  We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause you.
Order Cancellations
You can cancel or alter your order up until you submit the order. If your order has already been submitted, please contact the Customer Service Center at (877) 871-6755 (from 9 a.m. to 11:00 p.m., EST Monday through Friday (except holidays), and 9:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m., EST Saturday & Sunday) to cancel or alter the order. Once your order has been shipped, you will no longer be to cancel or alter the order. Instead, once your order arrives, you will need to follow the returns procedure in our Return Policy.
If you have a problem with any part of your order, please e-mail our Customer Service Center. Please include your name and order number or call our toll-free customer service number at (877) 871-6755.
Shipping
Read our shipping policy here.
Returns Restrictions
You may return any item you purchased on HarmanAudio.com, within 30 calendar days of your package being delivered, subject to the terms & exceptions below.
We will gladly exchange your product for the same model (subject to availability) or give you a refund for the full amount of the merchandise including taxes. Gift wrap and shipping charges are not refundable.
Personalized product exclusion: Once personalized orders have been processed, they cannot be cancelled or returned.
A return authorization is required for any exchange or refund. Any product shipped to us without a return authorization will be returned to the sender address. Once you obtain a return authorization, we will provide you with a return shipping label. You are responsible to securely pack the product and all the original contents. We strongly recommend that you use the original packaging, if available.
To return a product, click here.
For warranty service, click here.
Security & Privacy
Our site uses the industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure the safety of your Internet transactions. SSL encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name and address, to prevent decoding. To verify the security of your connection, check the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When you are accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https".
Information you provide during transactions on this Web site are confidential. Please read our Privacy Policy for more information on the data we collect and how we use it.
Gift Cards
Use of Harman Gift Cards are subject to the Gift Cards’ terms and conditions of use.
Promotions
Use of promotional codes, discounts, coupons or similar promotions are subject to that promotion’s terms and conditions. To be eligible for a specific promotion, your order must be submitted within the specified promotion period. Unless otherwise expressly stated in the applicable promotion’s terms and conditions, no more than one promotion may be applied to an order.
Secondary Navigation
Contact Us
FAQs
Privacy & Security
Privacy Policy
Security Policy
Ordering
Checkout
We noticed that you already have products in your cart. In order to add spare parts we have to empty your current cart.
Do you wish to continue?
Yes
No
Warning
×
We noticed that you already have spare parts in your cart. In order to add new products we have to empty your current cart.
Do you wish to continue?
If you are using a screen reader and are having problems using this website, please call (877) 871-6755 for assistance.
© 2020 Harman International Industries, Incorporated. All rights reserved.
More about cookies
Hide
I Agree
More about cookies
